=Deity of Love= =Episode 14=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 14 =
I have no idea of what Puti Lotus looks like.
ليس لدي أي فكرة عما يبدو عليه بوتي لوتس.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Even if you should travel around the world to find it,
حتى لو كان عليك السفر حول العالم للعثور عليه ،
I'm always by your side.
أنا دائما بجانبك.
Look.
نظرة.
Kongming Lantern.
كونغ مينغ فانوس.
Xiaoqing,
شياو تشينغ ،
follow me.
اتبعني.
When you put the lanterns on the water,
عندما تضع الفوانيس على الماء ،
you can make whatever you are thinking about
يمكنك القيام بكل ما تفكر فيه
come true.
سيتحقق.
Really?
هل حقا؟
The belief in a thing makes it happen.
الإيمان بشيء ما يجعله يحدث.
Try it.
جربها.
Look.
نظرة.
Is it pretty?
هل هذا جميل؟
Yes.
نعم.
Quite pretty.
جميلة جدا.
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
Brother Xiuning.
الأخ Xiuning.
Oh!
أوه!
Miss Xiaoqing.
ملكة جمال شياو تشينغ.
You again?
انت مرة اخرى؟
Who asked you to come?
من طلب منك المجيء؟
Ah!
آه!
We are neighbors.
نحن جيران.
And it's Dragon Boat Festival today.
وهو اليوم مهرجان قوارب التنين.
Why not have a good time together?
لماذا لا تقضي وقتًا ممتعًا معًا؟
Ling'er is right.
Ling'er على حق.
Oh.
أوه.
Miss Xiaoqing.
ملكة جمال شياو تشينغ.
I brought you
أنا جلبت لكم
my favorite realgar wine.
نبيذ ريجار المفضل لدي.
It's delicious. You can have a try.
إنه لذيذ.  يمكنك المحاولة.
Take it away.
خذه بعيدا.
You dare not drink realgar wine.
أنت لا تجرؤ على شرب نبيذ الغار.
Are you afraid?
هل انت خائف؟
Only demons...
فقط الشياطين ...
Hey.
يا.
Brother Xiuning, look at her.
الأخ Xiuning ، انظر إليها.
I helped her out of kindness.
لقد ساعدتها بدافع اللطف.
But she did that to me.
لكنها فعلت ذلك بي.
Get your hands off me.
ابعد يداك عني.
You want a drink?
تريد مشروب؟
I'll drink with you.
سأشرب معك.
Li Xiuning.
لي شيونينغ.
I'm here to propose a toast to Miss Xiaoqing.
أنا هنا لأقترح نخب الآنسة شياو تشينغ.
Does it have anything to do with you?
هل له علاقة بك؟
Are you afraid?
هل انت خائف؟
No, totally not.
لا ، لا.
If you lose,
لو خسرت،
stay away from Miss Xiaoqing.
ابتعد عن الآنسة شياو تشينغ.
Deal.
صفقة.
And if you lose,
وإذا خسرت ،
never step into Qingyun Valley again.
لا تخطو إلى وادي تشينغيون مرة أخرى.
You...you win.
أنت ... تفوز.
You loser...
أنت فاشل...
Brother Xiuning.
الأخ Xiuning.
Li Xiuning.
لي شيونينغ.
My lord.
ربي.
You haven't summoned me
أنت لم تستدعوني
in recent days.
في الايام الاخيرة.
Help me find Li Xiuning.
ساعدني في العثور على Li Xiuning.
I need his power and blood.
أحتاج إلى قوته ودمه.
I will definitely bring him here.
بالتأكيد سأجلبه هنا.
Don't let me down.
لا تخذلني.
If someone resists,
إذا قاوم شخص ما ،
just remind them of
فقط ذكرهم
the fear of being dominated by demons.
الخوف من هيمنة الشياطين.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)